Let's try making a couple of changes to this project.
このプロジェクトにいくつか変更を加えてみましょう。
Along the way, I'll show you some useful features around Claude Code.
その過程で、Claude Code の便利な機能をいくつかご紹介します。
The first thing I'd like to do is move this placeholder text over
まず、このプレースホルダーテキストを
here on the left-hand side down to the center of this panel.
左側からこのパネルの中央に移動させたいと思います。
To help Claude understand exactly what content I want
Claude に私が移動させたいコンテンツを正確に理解してもらうために、
moved, I'm going to take a screenshot of
その部分のスクリーンショットを撮り、
that area right there, and then I'm going to paste
それを Ctrl V を使って Claude Code に貼り付けます。
it into Claude Code using Ctrl V.
Mac OS で使い慣れている Command-V ではなく、Control-V であることに注意してください。Control-V は
Note that it's Control-V and not Command-V
特にスクリーンショットを貼り付けるために使用されます。
that you might be used to on Mac OS. Control-V is
そして、Claude にそのプレースホルダーを中央揃えにするよう依頼できます。
used specifically to paste in a screenshot. I
少し検索した後、Claude はスタイリングの更新を行うことができました。
can then ask Claude to center that placeholder. After
そしてブラウザに戻ると、うまくいきました。
a little bit of searching, Claude is able to make the styling update.
次にこのアプリで変更したいことを示します。
And then back inside the browser, yeah, looks great. Let
タイトルと説明を表示するカードコンポーネントをリクエストします。
me show you the next thing I would like to change in this app. I'm going to ask
カードは問題なく生成されますが、一つ気になることがあります。
for a card component that displays a title and some description.
チャットインターフェースの左側には String Replace Editor があります。
The card is generated without any issue, but there is one
その小さなパネルは
awkward thing. On left hand side in the chat interface,
ファイルが作成中であることをユーザーに示すためのものですが、
there's String Replace Editor. That little panel
現在、バックグラウンドで使われているツールに対して非常に技術的な用語
right there is meant to indicate to the user that a file is being
である「String Replace Editor」を使用しています。
created. But right now it's using a very technical term
このテキストをよりユーザーフレンドリーなものにして、
String Replace Editor for the tool that is being used behind the scenes.
ファイルが作成されていることとファイル名を示すようにしたいです。
I would like to show a user a little more friendly text here and
そしてもちろん、このチャットボットがファイルを編集したり、
just tell the user that a file is being created and the name of
削除したりする場合も考慮する必要があります。
the file. And of course, we should also handle cases where
Claude の注意を引くために、ここでもこの部分のスクリーンショットを撮り、
maybe this chatbot is editing a file or deleting
それが何を指しているのか正確に理解できるようにします。
a file and other stuff like that. To help guide Claude's
そして、ここに画像を貼り付けて、
attention, I'm going to once again take a screenshot of this so
Claude にその特定のテキストをよりユーザーフレンドリーなメッセージに置き換えるように依頼します。
it understands exactly what I'm talking about. Then, back
これは少し難しいタスクで、
over here, I'm going to paste that image in and ask Claude
Claude にはこのプロジェクトでかなりのリサーチを行ってもらう必要があります。
to replace that particular text with some more
Claude により難しいタスクを与える際には、
user-friendly message. Now, this is a little
Claude の知能を簡単に向上させる方法が2つあります。
bit of a tricky task that will require Claude to do
一つ目の方法は、プランモードを有効にすることです。
a decent amount of research in this project to complete.
プランモードは、Shift-Tab を 2 回押すか、
Whenever you give Claude a harder task, there are two
ファイル編集の自動承認が有効になっている場合は 1 回押すだけで有効になります。
ways that you can easily boost Claude's intelligence. The
プランモードでは、Claude はプロジェクトのコンテンツについて
first way is to enable Plan mode. Plan mode
より多くのリサーチを行い、
is enabled by pressing Shift-Tab twice, or
より多くのファイルを読み込み、タスクを完了する方法についての詳細な計画を立てます。
just once if you are already auto-accepting file edits.
計画を完了した後、Claude はタスクを完了するために何をするかを正確に伝えます。
In Plan mode, Claude will do much more research
その時点で、この計画を承認することもできます。Claude はそれを実装します。
over the contents of your project, reading more files
あるいは、Claude を何らかの形でリダイレクトすることもできます。
and coming up with a detailed plan on how to complete your
例えば、ファイルを見落としたり、
task. After completing the plan, Claude will
あるシナリオを考慮しなかったりした場合です。
tell you exactly what it wants to do to complete your task.
Claude の知能を向上させる2つ目の方法は、思考を有効にすることです。
At that point, you can either accept this plan, and Claude will
これは Claude の拡張思考機能をオンにし、
implement it, or you can redirect Claude in some
特定のタスクについてより深く推論できるようにします。
way, maybe it missed some file, or didn't consider
思考を有効にするには、いくつかの異なるトリガーフレーズがあります。
some scenario. The second way in which we can boost
それぞれが Claude により大きなトークン予算を付与し、
Claude's intelligence is by enabling thinking. This
それを思考に利用できるようにします。
turns on Claude's extended thinking feature, allowing
これがより難しいタスクであることを考慮すると、
it to reason more about a particular task. To
Claude に実装する最善の方法について「ウルトラシンク」させるとよいでしょう。
enable thinking, there are a handful of different trigger phrases.
理解すべき最後の点は、計画と思考は一緒に使用できるということです。
Each one gives Claude a progressively larger token
したがって、このウルトラシンクに加えて、プランモードもオンにします。
budget to think with. Given that this is a trickier task,
そして、これを実行して、どれだけうまく機能するか見てみましょう。
I might ask Claude to ultra-think about the best way to implement
ここで、計画と思考のどちらを使うべきか疑問に思うかもしれません。
it. The last thing to understand is that planning
これら2つを、広さと深さの処理として考えてください。
and thinking can be used together. So in addition to
プランモードは、コードベースの広範な理解を必要とするタスクで、
this ultra-think, I'm going to also turn on Plan mode
異なる領域を確認する必要がある場合に役立ちます。
as well. And now I'm going to run this and we'll see how well
また、完了までに複数のステップが必要なタスクにも役立ちます。
Claude can implement this feature. Now, you might
一方、思考は
be wondering when you should use planning and when you should use
特定の複雑なロジックの部分に焦点を当てる場合や、
thinking. Think of these two as handling
困難なバグをトラブルシューティングする場合に役立ちます。
breadth-first depth. Planning mode is useful
次に考えられる質問は、
when you have a task that requires a wide understanding
常に思考と計画を有効にすべきかどうかです。
of your codebase and requires looking at different areas.
もちろん、そうすることもできます。計画と思考は追加のトークンを消費するため、
It's also useful when working on a task that requires several
使用にはコストがかかることを覚えておいてください。
steps to complete. Thinking, on either hand, is
数分作業した後、機能は完了したようです。
useful when you are focusing on a particular tricky
エディタに戻ってテストしてみましょう。
bit of logic or troubleshooting a difficult
すぐに、以前よりも優れたステータス情報が表示されます。
bug. The second question you might have is whether
ユーザーはファイルが作成中であることが伝えられます。
you should just enable thinking and planning all the time.
フォローアップのリクエストを送信した場合、
Well, you certainly can, just keep in mind that planning
例えばタイトルを変更するように依頼した場合、
and thinking consume additional tokens, so there
フォローアップでそのファイルの編集に関する何かが表示されることを願っています。
is a cost associated with using them. After
はい、できました。アプリの jsx ファイルを編集しています。
a couple of minutes of work, it looks like the feature is complete. So
Claude はこの機能を実装するのに成功したと言えます。
I'm going to go back over to my editor and test this out. So
このプロジェクトに変更を加えたので、変更をコミットする必要があります。
right away, we can see that we get some better status information here
Claude Code は優れた Git アシスタントです。
than what we have before. Users are now being told that a file
変更をステージングしてコミットするように依頼すると、
is being created. And if I send in a followed request,
わかりやすいコミットメッセージを書いてくれます。
maybe to change the title. Hopefully
したがって、Git の変更をコミットすることができます。
now on the follow-up, we'll see something about editing that file.
Claude Code は信頼できる Git アシスタントです。
So there we go. So now we're editing the app.jsx file.
変更をステージングしてコミットするように指示すると、
Well, I would say Claude definitely succeeded in implementing
わかりやすいコミットメッセージを作成してくれます。